What is this?
这是什么？
In my class Jenny her parents are the owners of the house
我班上的珍妮 她的父母是这房子的主人
The tenants have just moved out so they don't have a chance to fix it
租户刚搬出去 所以他们还没机会整修呢
But I have to show it to you right away
但我必须立刻给你看
It obviously needs to be painted but.
很明显 它需要刷漆 整修 但是…
- Look at the scenery - beautiful scenery.
-看那景色 -很美的景色
Look over there? that's your coffee shop
看那边？那是你的咖啡店
- Really - five blocks away
-真是 -五个街区远
There are two bedrooms and a perfect little kitchen bathroom.
后面有两个卧室 一个完美的小厨房 浴室…
- Look at the ceiling - isn't it spectacular?
-看看天花板 -不壮观吗？
I don't want them to fix the humble grandeur
我都不想让他们整修了 这种简陋自带壮丽